Mercury Press Records
Mercury Press Records
- Fantasy and Science Fiction (Part II)
  - Production records
    - Galley and page proofs
      - Nelson, Starr
        - "Sonnets in a Moonship" (Box 86)
      - Nourse, Alan E.
        - "The Canvas Bag" (Box 86)
        - "The Expert Touch" (Box 86)
      - Novotny, John
        - "The Angry Peter Brindle" (Box 86)
        - "The Bourbon Lake" (Box 86)
        - "The Tin Halo" (Box 86)
      - Oesterreicher, Arthur
        - "Broken Circuit" (Box 86)
      - Oliver, Chad
        - "Pilgrimage" (Box 86)
        - "The Wind Blows Free" (Box 86)
      - Oliver, Chad and Beaumont, Charles
        - "The Last Word" (Box 86)
      - Ottum, Bob
        - "Chirp Me a Story" (Box 86)
      - Porges, Arthur
        - "The Logic of Rufus Weir" (Box 86)
      - Rigsby, Howard
        - "One Fine Day" (Box 86)
      - Roberts, Jane
        - "The Chestnut Beads" (Box 86)
      - Roberts, Mary-Carter
        - "One Sent" (Box 86)
      - Rogers, Kay
        - "The Bitterness of Ghoril" (Box 86)
      - St. Clair, Eric
        - "The Motorman's Glove" (Box 86)
      - Seabright, Idris
        - "Asking" (Box 86)
        - "Change the Sky" (Box 86)
        - "Eithne" (Box 86)
        - "Personal Monster" (Box 86)
      - Seeley, Mabel
        - "The Footprint" (Box 86)
      - Shaara, Michael
        - "Grenville's Planet" (Box 86)
      - Sheckley, Robert
        - "The Prize of Peril" (Box 86)
        - "The Slow Season" (Box 86)
      - Shepley, John
        - "Gorilla Suit" (Box 87)
      - Smith, Evelyn E.
        - "At Last I've Found You" (Box 87)
        - "Daxbr Baxbr" (Box 87)
      - Stanton, Will
        - "The Last Present" (Box 87)
      - Sturgeon, Theodore
        - "The Widget, the Wadget, and Boff" (Box 87)
      - Sullivan, Edward S.
        - "The 8:29" (Box 87)
      - Tenn, William
        - "Eastward Ho!" (Box 87)
      - Thurber, James
        - "Interview With a Lemming" (Box 87)
      - United States Air Force
        - "Unidentified Aerial Objects" (Box 87)
      - Walton, Bryce
        - "The Midway" (Box 87)
      - Webb, Charles T.
        - "Bem" (Box 87)
        - "Special Talent" (Box 87)
      - Wellman, Manly Wade
        - "The Little Black Train" (Box 87)
        - "Walk Like a Mountain" (Box 87)
      - White, E. B.
        - "The Hour of Letdown" (Box 87)
      - Williams, Jay
        - "Mr. Guthrie's Cold War" (Box 87)
      - Wilson, Richard
        - "Don't Fence Me In" (Box 87)
      - Winslow, Thyra Samter
        - "Rudolph" (Box 87)
      - Wodehouse, P. G.
        - "Unpleasantness at Bludleigh Court" (Box 87)
      - Young, Robert F.
        - "Thirty Days Had September" (Box 87)
    - Layouts, undated (Box 87)
    - Lists of fantasy books, undated (Box 87)
    - Press releases, undated (Box 87)
    - Production schedules, 1950-1956 (Box 87)
    - Sales statistics and graphs, undated (Box 87)
    - Tables of contents, 1951-1969 (Box 87)
    - Tear sheets
      - Abernathy, Robert
        - "Heirs Apparent" (Box 87)
      - Aldiss, Brian W.
        - "Poor Little Warrior!" (Box 87)
      - Anderson, Poul
        - "Backwardness" (Box 87)
        - "The Immortal Game" (Box 87)
      - Arthur, Robert
        - "Postpaid to Paradise" (Box 87)
      - Ballard, J. G.
        - "Build Up" (Box 87)
        - "Mobile" (Box 87)
      - Bester, Alfred
        - "Fondly Fahrenheit" (Box 87)
        - "The Men Who Murdered Mohammed" (Box 87)
        - "Starlight" (Box 87)
      - Boucher, Anthony
        - "Snulbug" (Box 87)
      - Bradbury, Ray
        - "All Summer in a Day" (Box 87)
      - Bretnor, R.
        - "Maybe Just a Little One" (Box 87)
      - Cartmill, Cleve
        - "Huge Beast" (Box 87)
      - Davidson, Avram
        - "My Boy Friend's Name is Jello" (Box 87)
      - Dickens, Charles
        - "The Rat That Could Speak" (Box 87)
      - Dryfoos, Dave
        - "Man" (Box 87)
      - Farmer, Jose
        - "Attitudes" (Box 87)
      - Friborg, Albert Compton
        - "Careless Love" (Box 87)
      - Galouye, Daniel F.
        - "Sanctuary" (Box 87)
      - Goulart, Ron
        - "A New Los" (Box 87)
      - Gresham, William Lindsay
        - "The Star Gypsies" (Box 87)
      - Griffith, Ann Warren
        - "Captive Audience" (Box 87)
      - Harness, Charles L.
        - "Child by Chronos" (Box 87)
      - Heard, H. F.
        - "The Collector" (Box 87)
      - Henderson, Zenna
        - "Captivity" (Box 87)
      - Hubbard, P. M.
        - "Manuscript Found in a Vacuum" (Box 87)
      - Jackson, Shirley
        - "Bulletin" (Box 87)
        - "The Omen" (Box 87)
      - Kornbluth, C. M.
        - "I Never Ast no Favors" (Box 87)
        - "Theory of Rocketry" (Box 87)
      - Leiber, Fritz
        - "A Deskful of Girls" (Box 87)
      - Lewis, C. S.
        - "Ministering Angels" (Box 87)
      - McClintic, Winona
        - "In the Days of Our Fathers" (Box 87)
      - McComas, J. Francis
        - "Brave New World" (Box 87)
      - Matheson, Richard
        - "Dress of White Silk" (Box 87)
      - Middleton, Richard
        - "Shepherd's Boy" (Box 87)
      - Moore, Ward
        - "Lot" (Box 87)
      - Nearing, H., Jr.
        - "The Maladjusted Classroom" (Box 87)
        - "The Mathematical Voodoo" (Box 87)
      - Nelson, Alan
        - "Narapoia" (Box 87)
      - Porges, Arthur
        - "1.98" (Box 87)
      - Ready, W. B.
        - "Devlin" (Box 87)
      - Reed, Kit
        - "The Wait" (Box 87)
      - Rogers, Kay
        - "Experiment" (Box 87)
      - Schoenfeld, Howard
        - "Built Up Logically" (Box 87)
      - Seabright, Idris
        - "The Listening Child" (Box 87)
        - "New Ritual" (Box 87)
      - Sheckley, Robert
        - "The Accountant" (Box 87)
      - Shepley, John
        - "Gorilla Suit" (Box 87)
      - Stanton, Will
        - "Barney" (Box 87)
      - Verne, Jules
        - "Gil Braltar" (Box 87)
      - Wellman, Manly Wade
        - "The Little Black Train" (Box 87)
        - "Vandy, Vandy" (Box 87)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 87)
- True Crime Detective (Part II)
  - Editorial records
    - Literary manuscripts
      - Unidentified (Box 88)
      - Ainsworth, Rex
        - "Clue of the Severed Hand" (Box 88)
        - "Her Fatal Fiancé" (Box 88)
      - Bailey, Seth
        - "Case of the Two Solutions" (Box 88)
      - Brannon, William T.
        - "The Curse of Death" (Box 88)
        - "Master of Chicanery" (Box 88)
        - "Rendezvous at Rondout" (Box 88)
      - Boucher, Anthony
        - "The Borderlands of Sanity" (Box 88)
      - Brennan, Ray
        - "Somebody Knows" (Box 88)
      - Brennan, Richard
        - "The Case of the Talking Reindeer" (Box 88)
      - deFord, Miriam Allen
        - "Murder for Sport" (Box 88)
        - "The Murderer Was a Lady" (Box 88)
        - "The Reluctant Lover" (Box 88)
      - de la Torre, Lillian
        - "The First Locked Room" (Box 88)
      - Doradin, Edward
        - "The Killer Who Wasn't There" (Box 88)
      - Doyle, Dorothy D.
        - "Portrait of the Monster as a Young Man" (Box 88)
      - Fredericks, Richard W.
        - "Berlin's Torso Mystery" (Box 88)
      - Gitlin, Irving
        - "Mr. Big and the Waterfront" (Box 88)
      - Hite, Jackson
        - "The Orange Daniel Webster" (Box 88)
      - Hoffman, Richard
        - "The Untold Story of Martha" (Box 88)
      - Holbrook, Stewart H.
        - "Cleopatra of Puget Sound" (Box 88)
        - "Dead Man's Bounty" (Box 88)
      - Jesse, F. Tennyson
        - "The Importance of Spelling" (Box 88)
        - "Mother and Son" (Box 88)
        - "Murder in the King's Household" (Box 88)
      - Jordan, Henry
        - "Dead-End" (Box 88)
      - Kelly, M. R.
        - "America's Jack-The-Ripper" (Box 88)
        - "The Case of the Quiet Co-Ed" (Box 88)
      - Lipsky, Eleazar
        - "The Shield of the Innocent" (Box 88)
      - McComas, J. Francis
        - "Until You Are Dead..." (Box 88)
      - Mullady, Frank
        - "Judgment for a Messiah", 2 folders (Box 89)
        - "Murder Without Reason" (Box 89)
        - "Murderers on the Loose" (Box 89)
        - "The Red Circle Murders" (Box 89)
      - Offord, Lenore Glen
        - "The Murder of Maria Marten or The Red Barn Revisited" (Box 89)
      - Oursler, Will
        - "Ocey and the Ladies in Black" (Box 89)
      - Oursler, Will and Barry, Jerome
        - "Winston Churchill's Strangest Case" (Box 89)
      - Palmer, Stuart
        - "Death and the Farmer's Daughter" (Box 89)
        - "The Ministering Angel" (Box 89)
        - "Nancy Clem's Secret" (Box 89)
        - "Once Aboard the Lugger" (Box 89)
        - "The Quick and the Dead" (Box 89)
      - Parkhill, Forbes
        - "The Strange World of Alex Miller" (Box 89)
      - Patterson, Bob
        - "The Antoine Case" (Box 89)
      - Phillips, Joseph
        - "They Write Their Own Convictions" (Box 89)
      - Radin, Edward D.
        - "Catspaw" (Box 89)
        - "Death on Mount Torment" (Box 89)
        - "The Invisible Cord" (Box 89)
        - "It Happened in Flushing" (Box 89)
      - Rice, Earl D.
        - "Murder by Conscience" (Box 89)
      - Roscoe, Burton
        - "The Affair of Mr. X" (Box 89)
      - Ross, Irwin
        - "Boom in Counterfeiting", 2 foldes (Box 89)
      - Shay, Joseph A.
        - "A Rake's Progress" (Box 89)
      - Smith, Laurence Dwight
        - "The Incredible Dr. Brandeburg" (Box 89)
      - Sullivan, Edward S.
        - "Assignment: Murder" (Box 89)
      - Vega, Don Pancho
        - "Twist With a Twist" (Box 89)
      - Wanger, Walter
        - "What I Found in Jail", 3 folders (Box 89)
      - Wallace, Kevin
        - "The Great Screwball Bank Robbery", 2 folders (Box 89)
      - Wellman, Manly Wade
        - "Bender's Orchard" (Box 90)
        - "The General Dies at Dusk" (Box 90)
        - "Hex Marks the Murder" (Box 90)
      - Zolotow, Maurice
        - "Was the Mindreader Murdered?" (Box 90)
  - Financial records
    - Check orders, 1952-1953 (Box 90)
    - Inventories, 1952-1953 (Box 90)
    - Manuscript costs, 1952-1953 (Box 90)
    - Royalty statements, 1953-1954 (Box 90)
  - Production records
    - Covers, 1952-1953 (Box 90)
    - Fillers, undated (Box 90)
    - Form letters, undated (Box 90)
    - Galley and page proofs
      - Fragments (Box 90)
      - Allen, Beech
        - "Appointment With Death" (Box 90)
      - Armour, Fred
        - "The Man Who Couldn't Stay Dead" (Box 90)
      - Boucher, Anthony (?)
        - "Here's the Answer" (Box 90)
        - "Introduction" (Box 90)
      - Creedmore, William R.
        - "The Vengeance of Mother India" (Box 90)
      - Desmarais, Ovide
        - "Terror on Vinicum Road" (Box 90)
      - Dinneen, Joseph F.
        - "Murder in Massachusetts" (Box 90)
      - Grey, Wilton
        - "The Clue of the Blue Serpent" (Box 90)
      - Holbrook, Stewart A.
        - "Cleopatra of Puget Sound" (Box 90)
      - Jesse, F. Tennyson
        - "Mother and Son" (Box 90)
      - Lustgarten, Edgar
        - "Small H., Mr. Pigott!" (Box 90)
      - Markey, Morris
        - "The Mysterious Death of Starr Faithfull" (Box 90)
      - Martin, John Bartlow
        - "I Was a Successful Burglar" (Box 90)
      - Mullady, Frank
        - "Judgment for a Messiah" (Box 90)
      - Oursler, Will and Barry, Jerome
        - "Winston Churchill's Strangest Case" (Box 90)
      - Palmer, Stuart
        - "The Ministering Angel" (Box 90)
      - Phillips, Joseph
        - "They Wrote Their Own Convictions" (Box 90)
      - Radin, Edward D.
        - "Catspaw" (Box 90)
      - Ross, Irwin
        - "Boom in Counterfeiting" (Box 90)
      - Roughead, William
        - "The Merrett Mystery" (Box 90)
      - Taylor, Herbert Hall
        - "The Pastor's Crime" (Box 90)
      - Wallace, Kevin
        - "The Great Screwball Bank Robbery" (Box 90)
      - Wellman, Manly Wade
        - "Hex Marks the Murder" (Box 90)
      - Whitman, Howard
        - "The Crime of Rape" (Box 90)
  - Production schedules
    - 1952 (Box 90)